# Elias **Matta**

Junior Web Developer

0421 224 777

emtech.projectdevelopment @gmail

github.com/emTech-projectDevelopment

linkedin.com/in/eliasmatta-b28858227/

March 2022

Dear Sir / Madam,

My name is Elias Matta. I write to you in regards to the position advertised on seek for a junior web developer. I am a recent graduate of a Junior Web Developer Bootcamp run by Generation Australia in conjunction with AcademyXi.

I believe i am the right applicant for the position as I am a competent learner and have a good grasp on concepts and syntax used in tech. I have a good attention to detail and great problem solving skills that apply critical thinking when seeking solutions.

My strength is to learn by doing and I have been able to create and debug projects to showcase my understanding in various technologies.

I have been a qualified chef for twenty five years and have an extensive resume. As i plan to begin a new career in tech the resume attached only includes my last current position in the field. A detailed resume of my cooking career can be found on my github portfolio site. The link to this is found at the bottom of the cover letter or resume.

I look forward to hearing from you.

Kind regards,

Elias Matta

Portfolio Site https://emtech-projectdevelopment.github.io/Portfolio-site/



# Elias **Matta**

Junior Web Developer

- 0421 224 777
- emtech.projectdevelopment @gmail
- github.com/emTechprojectDevelopment
- linkedin.com/in/eliasmatta-b28858227/

# **Personal Skills**

Time management
Adaptability and Self-Learning
Honest and Accountable
Pateince and Problem-Solving
Empathetic and Gracious
Leader and motivator

## Skills

HTML SQL
CSS Cli
Javascript Git

Python Agile

NodeJs Scrum

Kivy / KV Bootstrap

React JS Vue JS

Google Arabic

Korean

# **Achievements**

# BiData - Python Kivy App

Designed and coded a personal Crypto Portfolio App

## DreamerSpeaker - VueJs

Learning to code a Bluetooth app for a meditation headset

#### **About me**

Motivated junior web developer, keen to collaborate and learn. I have always had a hunger for learning and knowledge. After learning different technologies used in the tech industry, i choose to use my past experiences and knowledge to further develop my skills in web development.

## Education

2021 - 2022	Junior Web Developer Bootcamp Graduate
	Generation Australia / AcademyXi
2012 - 2014	CodeCademy Tech Certificates Certificates showing an understanding and use of concepts can be found on my linkedIn profile.
2011 - 2012	Food Saftey Supervisor HACCP Certification
1998 - 2002	Commercial Catering Cert. 4  Qualififed Chef

# **Experience**

2018 - 2022

## Sous Chef - Cross Roads Hotel

I have been in the Cross Roads family for almost five years and enjoy my work there. My position affords me the time to teach and motivate the team. This is a big venue and managing a big team has been a great achievement in my career.

## 2022

## Founder of emTech Project Development

Conceived emTech as a E-commerce Brand and was able to adapt and grow as client requirements changed and projects grew complex.

2021 - 2022

## **Portfolio Site**

https://emtech-projectdevelopment.github.io/Portfolio-site/